{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n6(x + 5)^2 - 24 \u003d 0", "answer": "-3, -7", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n6(x + 5)^2 - 24 \u003d 0\n6(x + 5)^2 \u003d 24\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 5)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 5 \u003d +√(4) or x + 5 \u003d -√(4)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n6(x + 6)^2 - 48 \u003d 0", "answer": "-6 + 2√(2), -6 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n6(x + 6)^2 - 48 \u003d 0\n6(x + 6)^2 \u003d 48\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 6)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 6 \u003d +√(8) or x + 6 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x - 2)^2 - 64 \u003d 0", "answer": "2 + 2√(2), 2 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x - 2)^2 - 64 \u003d 0\n8(x - 2)^2 \u003d 64\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 2)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 2 \u003d + √(8) or x - 2 \u003d - √(8)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 1)^2 - 56 \u003d 0", "answer": "-1 + 2√(2), -1 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 1)^2 - 56 \u003d 0\n7(x + 1)^2 \u003d 56\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 1)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 1 \u003d +√(8) or x + 1 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 64 \u003d 0", "answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 64 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 64\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(64) or x \u003d -√(64)\nx \u003d +8 or x \u003d -8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 484 \u003d 0", "answer": "22, -22", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 484 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 484\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(484) or x \u003d -√(484)\nx \u003d +22 or x \u003d -22", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x - 2)^2 - 24 \u003d 0", "answer": "2 + √(3), 2 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x - 2)^2 - 24 \u003d 0\n8(x - 2)^2 \u003d 24\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 2)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 2 \u003d + √(3) or x - 2 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x - 2)^2 - 12 \u003d 0", "answer": "2 + √(3), 2 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x - 2)^2 - 12 \u003d 0\n4(x - 2)^2 \u003d 12\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 2)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 2 \u003d + √(3) or x - 2 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 2)^2 - 42 \u003d 0", "answer": "2 + √(6), 2 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 2)^2 - 42 \u003d 0\n7(x - 2)^2 \u003d 42\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 2)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 2 \u003d + √(6) or x - 2 \u003d - √(6)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 8)^2 - 81 \u003d 0", "answer": "11, 5", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 8)^2 - 81 \u003d 0\n9(x - 8)^2 \u003d 81\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 8)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 8 \u003d + √(9) or x - 8 \u003d - √(9)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 8)^2 - 48 \u003d 0", "answer": "-8 + √(6), -8 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 8)^2 - 48 \u003d 0\n8(x + 8)^2 \u003d 48\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(6) or x + 8 \u003d -√(6)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x + 2)^2 - 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "-2 + √(2), -2 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x + 2)^2 - 4 \u003d 0\n2(x + 2)^2 \u003d 4\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(2) or x + 2 \u003d -√(2)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 324 \u003d 0", "answer": "18, -18", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 324 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 324\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(324) or x \u003d -√(324)\nx \u003d +18 or x \u003d -18", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 6)^2 - 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "6 + √(3), 6 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 6)^2 - 6 \u003d 0\n2(x - 6)^2 \u003d 6\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 6)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 6 \u003d + √(3) or x - 6 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 3)^2 - 110 \u003d 0", "answer": "3 + √(10), 3 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 3)^2 - 110 \u003d 0\n11(x - 3)^2 \u003d 110\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 3)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 3 \u003d + √(10) or x - 3 \u003d - √(10)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x - 6)^2 - 90 \u003d 0", "answer": "9, 3", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x - 6)^2 - 90 \u003d 0\n10(x - 6)^2 \u003d 90\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 6)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 6 \u003d + √(9) or x - 6 \u003d - √(9)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 16 \u003d 0", "answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 16 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 16\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(16) or x \u003d -√(16)\nx \u003d +4 or x \u003d -4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 10)^2 - 63 \u003d 0", "answer": "10 + √(7), 10 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 10)^2 - 63 \u003d 0\n9(x - 10)^2 \u003d 63\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 10)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 10 \u003d + √(7) or x - 10 \u003d - √(7)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x + 7)^2 - 110 \u003d 0", "answer": "-7 + √(10), -7 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x + 7)^2 - 110 \u003d 0\n11(x + 7)^2 \u003d 110\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 7)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 7 \u003d +√(10) or x + 7 \u003d -√(10)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x + 8)^2 - 16 \u003d 0", "answer": "-8 + 2√(2), -8 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x + 8)^2 - 16 \u003d 0\n2(x + 8)^2 \u003d 16\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(8) or x + 8 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0", "answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 196\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(196) or x \u003d -√(196)\nx \u003d +14 or x \u003d -14", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 16 \u003d 0", "answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 16 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 16\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(16) or x \u003d -√(16)\nx \u003d +4 or x \u003d -4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 3)^2 - 42 \u003d 0", "answer": "-3 + √(6), -3 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 3)^2 - 42 \u003d 0\n7(x + 3)^2 \u003d 42\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 3 \u003d +√(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 3)^2 - 36 \u003d 0", "answer": "5, 1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 3)^2 - 36 \u003d 0\n9(x - 3)^2 \u003d 36\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 3)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 3 \u003d + √(4) or x - 3 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0", "answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 121\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(121) or x \u003d -√(121)\nx \u003d +11 or x \u003d -11", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x + 3)^2 - 63 \u003d 0", "answer": "-3 + √(7), -3 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x + 3)^2 - 63 \u003d 0\n9(x + 3)^2 \u003d 63\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 3 \u003d +√(7) or x + 3 \u003d -√(7)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 1)^2 - 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "1 + √(2), 1 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 1)^2 - 4 \u003d 0\n2(x - 1)^2 \u003d 4\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 1)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 1 \u003d + √(2) or x - 1 \u003d - √(2)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 7)^2 - 21 \u003d 0", "answer": "-7 + √(3), -7 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 7)^2 - 21 \u003d 0\n7(x + 7)^2 \u003d 21\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 7)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 7 \u003d +√(3) or x + 7 \u003d -√(3)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x + 2)^2 - 90 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -5", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x + 2)^2 - 90 \u003d 0\n10(x + 2)^2 \u003d 90\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(9) or x + 2 \u003d -√(9)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x - 6)^2 - 12 \u003d 0", "answer": "8, 4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x - 6)^2 - 12 \u003d 0\n3(x - 6)^2 \u003d 12\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 6)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 6 \u003d + √(4) or x - 6 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 676 \u003d 0", "answer": "26, -26", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 676 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 676\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(676) or x \u003d -√(676)\nx \u003d +26 or x \u003d -26", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0", "answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 169\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(169) or x \u003d -√(169)\nx \u003d +13 or x \u003d -13", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 225 \u003d 0", "answer": "15, -15", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 225 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 225\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(225) or x \u003d -√(225)\nx \u003d +15 or x \u003d -15", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 900 \u003d 0", "answer": "30, -30", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 900 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 900\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(900) or x \u003d -√(900)\nx \u003d +30 or x \u003d -30", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 9)^2 - 9 \u003d 0", "answer": "10, 8", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 9)^2 - 9 \u003d 0\n9(x - 9)^2 \u003d 9\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 9)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 9 \u003d + √(1) or x - 9 \u003d - √(1)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 625 \u003d 0", "answer": "25, -25", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 625 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 625\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(625) or x \u003d -√(625)\nx \u003d +25 or x \u003d -25", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x - 10)^2 - 10 \u003d 0", "answer": "11, 9", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x - 10)^2 - 10 \u003d 0\n10(x - 10)^2 \u003d 10\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 10)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 10 \u003d + √(1) or x - 10 \u003d - √(1)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0", "answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 196\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(196) or x \u003d -√(196)\nx \u003d +14 or x \u003d -14", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 8)^2 - 18 \u003d 0", "answer": "11, 5", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 8)^2 - 18 \u003d 0\n2(x - 8)^2 \u003d 18\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 8)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 8 \u003d + √(9) or x - 8 \u003d - √(9)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n6(x + 1)^2 - 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "0, -2", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n6(x + 1)^2 - 6 \u003d 0\n6(x + 1)^2 \u003d 6\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 1)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 1 \u003d +√(1) or x + 1 \u003d -√(1)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 784 \u003d 0", "answer": "28, -28", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 784 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 784\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(784) or x \u003d -√(784)\nx \u003d +28 or x \u003d -28", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 7)^2 - 45 \u003d 0", "answer": "7 + √(5), 7 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 7)^2 - 45 \u003d 0\n9(x - 7)^2 \u003d 45\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 7)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 7 \u003d + √(5) or x - 7 \u003d - √(5)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 7)^2 - 14 \u003d 0", "answer": "7 + √(2), 7 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 7)^2 - 14 \u003d 0\n7(x - 7)^2 \u003d 14\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 7)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 7 \u003d + √(2) or x - 7 \u003d - √(2)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 3)^2 - 56 \u003d 0", "answer": "3 + 2√(2), 3 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 3)^2 - 56 \u003d 0\n7(x - 3)^2 \u003d 56\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 3)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 3 \u003d + √(8) or x - 3 \u003d - √(8)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 64 \u003d 0", "answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 64 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 64\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(64) or x \u003d -√(64)\nx \u003d +8 or x \u003d -8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 576 \u003d 0", "answer": "24, -24", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 576 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 576\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(576) or x \u003d -√(576)\nx \u003d +24 or x \u003d -24", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x - 4)^2 - 27 \u003d 0", "answer": "7, 1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x - 4)^2 - 27 \u003d 0\n3(x - 4)^2 \u003d 27\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(9) or x - 4 \u003d - √(9)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 676 \u003d 0", "answer": "26, -26", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 676 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 676\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(676) or x \u003d -√(676)\nx \u003d +26 or x \u003d -26", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x + 5)^2 - 9 \u003d 0", "answer": "-5 + √(3), -5 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x + 5)^2 - 9 \u003d 0\n3(x + 5)^2 \u003d 9\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 5)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 5 \u003d +√(3) or x + 5 \u003d -√(3)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 1)^2 - 28 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -3", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 1)^2 - 28 \u003d 0\n7(x + 1)^2 \u003d 28\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 1)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 1 \u003d +√(4) or x + 1 \u003d -√(4)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x + 10)^2 - 18 \u003d 0", "answer": "-10 + √(6), -10 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x + 10)^2 - 18 \u003d 0\n3(x + 10)^2 \u003d 18\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 10)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 10 \u003d +√(6) or x + 10 \u003d -√(6)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 361 \u003d 0", "answer": "19, -19", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 361 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 361\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(361) or x \u003d -√(361)\nx \u003d +19 or x \u003d -19", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0", "answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 196\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(196) or x \u003d -√(196)\nx \u003d +14 or x \u003d -14", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 8)^2 - 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "8 + √(3), 8 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 8)^2 - 6 \u003d 0\n2(x - 8)^2 \u003d 6\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 8)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 8 \u003d + √(3) or x - 8 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 225 \u003d 0", "answer": "15, -15", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 225 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 225\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(225) or x \u003d -√(225)\nx \u003d +15 or x \u003d -15", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 1)^2 - 42 \u003d 0", "answer": "1 + √(6), 1 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 1)^2 - 42 \u003d 0\n7(x - 1)^2 \u003d 42\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 1)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 1 \u003d + √(6) or x - 1 \u003d - √(6)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 2)^2 - 70 \u003d 0", "answer": "-2 + √(10), -2 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 2)^2 - 70 \u003d 0\n7(x + 2)^2 \u003d 70\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(10) or x + 2 \u003d -√(10)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 2)^2 - 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "2 + √(3), 2 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 2)^2 - 6 \u003d 0\n2(x - 2)^2 \u003d 6\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 2)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 2 \u003d + √(3) or x - 2 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 5)^2 - 64 \u003d 0", "answer": "-5 + 2√(2), -5 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 5)^2 - 64 \u003d 0\n8(x + 5)^2 \u003d 64\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 5)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 5 \u003d +√(8) or x + 5 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 5)^2 - 54 \u003d 0", "answer": "5 + √(6), 5 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 5)^2 - 54 \u003d 0\n9(x - 5)^2 \u003d 54\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 5)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 5 \u003d + √(6) or x - 5 \u003d - √(6)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 144 \u003d 0", "answer": "12, -12", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 144 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 144\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(144) or x \u003d -√(144)\nx \u003d +12 or x \u003d -12", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 100 \u003d 0", "answer": "10, -10", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 100 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 100\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(100) or x \u003d -√(100)\nx \u003d +10 or x \u003d -10", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x - 3)^2 - 25 \u003d 0", "answer": "3 + √(5), 3 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x - 3)^2 - 25 \u003d 0\n5(x - 3)^2 \u003d 25\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 3)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 3 \u003d + √(5) or x - 3 \u003d - √(5)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x + 10)^2 - 50 \u003d 0", "answer": "-10 + √(5), -10 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x + 10)^2 - 50 \u003d 0\n10(x + 10)^2 \u003d 50\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 10)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 10 \u003d +√(5) or x + 10 \u003d -√(5)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 9)^2 - 64 \u003d 0", "answer": "-9 + 2√(2), -9 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 9)^2 - 64 \u003d 0\n8(x + 9)^2 \u003d 64\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 9)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 9 \u003d +√(8) or x + 9 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x + 6)^2 - 72 \u003d 0", "answer": "-6 + 2√(2), -6 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x + 6)^2 - 72 \u003d 0\n9(x + 6)^2 \u003d 72\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 6)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 6 \u003d +√(8) or x + 6 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x + 10)^2 - 20 \u003d 0", "answer": "-10 + √(10), -10 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x + 10)^2 - 20 \u003d 0\n2(x + 10)^2 \u003d 20\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 10)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 10 \u003d +√(10) or x + 10 \u003d -√(10)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x + 1)^2 - 32 \u003d 0", "answer": "-1 + 2√(2), -1 - 2√(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x + 1)^2 - 32 \u003d 0\n4(x + 1)^2 \u003d 32\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 1)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 1 \u003d +√(8) or x + 1 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x - 6)^2 - 32 \u003d 0", "answer": "8, 4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x - 6)^2 - 32 \u003d 0\n8(x - 6)^2 \u003d 32\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 6)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 6 \u003d + √(4) or x - 6 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 361 \u003d 0", "answer": "19, -19", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 361 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 361\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(361) or x \u003d -√(361)\nx \u003d +19 or x \u003d -19", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 144 \u003d 0", "answer": "12, -12", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 144 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 144\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(144) or x \u003d -√(144)\nx \u003d +12 or x \u003d -12", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x - 7)^2 - 16 \u003d 0", "answer": "7 + √(2), 7 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x - 7)^2 - 16 \u003d 0\n8(x - 7)^2 \u003d 16\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 7)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 7 \u003d + √(2) or x - 7 \u003d - √(2)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 6)^2 - 63 \u003d 0", "answer": "6 + √(7), 6 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 6)^2 - 63 \u003d 0\n9(x - 6)^2 \u003d 63\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 6)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 6 \u003d + √(7) or x - 6 \u003d - √(7)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n6(x + 3)^2 - 54 \u003d 0", "answer": "0, -6", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n6(x + 3)^2 - 54 \u003d 0\n6(x + 3)^2 \u003d 54\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 3 \u003d +√(9) or x + 3 \u003d -√(9)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 10)^2 - 40 \u003d 0", "answer": "-10 + √(5), -10 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 10)^2 - 40 \u003d 0\n8(x + 10)^2 \u003d 40\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 10)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 10 \u003d +√(5) or x + 10 \u003d -√(5)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 729 \u003d 0", "answer": "27, -27", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 729 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 729\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(729) or x \u003d -√(729)\nx \u003d +27 or x \u003d -27", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 81 \u003d 0", "answer": "9, -9", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 81 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 81\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(81) or x \u003d -√(81)\nx \u003d +9 or x \u003d -9", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 8)^2 - 8 \u003d 0", "answer": "10, 6", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 8)^2 - 8 \u003d 0\n2(x - 8)^2 \u003d 8\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 8)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 8 \u003d + √(4) or x - 8 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 841 \u003d 0", "answer": "29, -29", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 841 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 841\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(841) or x \u003d -√(841)\nx \u003d +29 or x \u003d -29", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 5)^2 - 7 \u003d 0", "answer": "-4, -6", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 5)^2 - 7 \u003d 0\n7(x + 5)^2 \u003d 7\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 5)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 5 \u003d +√(1) or x + 5 \u003d -√(1)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 49 \u003d 0", "answer": "7, -7", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 49 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 49\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(49) or x \u003d -√(49)\nx \u003d +7 or x \u003d -7", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 144 \u003d 0", "answer": "12, -12", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 144 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 144\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(144) or x \u003d -√(144)\nx \u003d +12 or x \u003d -12", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 8)^2 - 48 \u003d 0", "answer": "-8 + √(6), -8 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 8)^2 - 48 \u003d 0\n8(x + 8)^2 \u003d 48\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(6) or x + 8 \u003d -√(6)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 484 \u003d 0", "answer": "22, -22", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 484 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 484\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(484) or x \u003d -√(484)\nx \u003d +22 or x \u003d -22", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 9)^2 - 63 \u003d 0", "answer": "9 + √(7), 9 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 9)^2 - 63 \u003d 0\n9(x - 9)^2 \u003d 63\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 9)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 9 \u003d + √(7) or x - 9 \u003d - √(7)\nSimplify and solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 900 \u003d 0", "answer": "30, -30", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 900 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 900\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(900) or x \u003d -√(900)\nx \u003d +30 or x \u003d -30", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 25 \u003d 0", "answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 25 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 25\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(25) or x \u003d -√(25)\nx \u003d +5 or x \u003d -5", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d"}
]}